http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly
(FOOTSTEPS ECHO)
(PLANE ENGINE ROARING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(BED SPRINGS CREAKING)
(MEN CHATTERING)
(WOMAN GASPS)
(WOMAN YELLING)
(MAN SPEAKS JAPANESE)
(MEN CHEER, LAUGH)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(MAN SHUSHES)
(SOBBING FADES)
(CRYING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(COUGHING)
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(PANTING)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(MAN SPEAKING OUTSIDE)
(MEN LAUGH)
(SPEED-DIALS NUMBER)
(LINE RINGING)
This is Detective Robertson.
Leave a message after the beep.
- (BEEPS)
- He knows. He knows.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
What's going on in there?
(POUNDS)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(GASPS)
(SPEED-DIALS NUMBER)
- (MEN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
- (LINE RINGS)
Hello. It's Edith...
GIRL: And Maisey.
EDITH: We are not home right now.
- Leave a message after the beep.
- Beep.
(BEEPS)
(HANGS UP)
MAN: Ooh.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Get the fuck out here!
Get out here now!
(MEN TALKING)
I'm coming in!
(GUNSHOT)
(DISTANT SOUNDS ECHOING)
(MEN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(STEREO PLAYS:
"WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS")
(GUNFIRE)
♪ Good tidings to you ♪
♪ And a happy New Year... ♪
- (GROANS)
- (MUSIC QUIETS)
♪ And a happy New Year ♪
♪ Good tidings to you ♪
- ♪ (PISTOL CLICKING) ♪
- ♪ Wherever you are ♪
- ♪ (MAN GRUNTING) ♪
- ♪ Good tidings for Christmas ♪
♪ And a happy New Year ♪
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
- ♪ (GAGS) ♪
- ♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
♪ and a happy New Year ♪
(THUMPING ON CEILING)
WOMAN 1: What the hell
is all that noise?
Cheese and crackers,
keep it down.
Really?
- (SIGHS)
- (SONG STOPS)
♪ (STEREO PLAYS: "GOD REST
YOU MERRY, GENTLEMEN") ♪
♪ ...merry, gentlemen E ♪
♪ Let nothing you dismay... ♪
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
WOMAN 2:
Hey, is everything okay in there?
♪ ...was born ♪
♪ on Christmas Day... ♪
Yeah.
♪ To save us all ♪
♪ from Satan's power ♪
- ♪ Oh, my God. ♪
- ♪ When we were gone astray ♪
♪ O tidings ♪
- ♪ I'm sorry. ♪
- ♪ Of comfort and joy ♪
♪ Comfort and joy ♪
♪ O tidings of comfort and joy... ♪
(PANTING)
(SPEED-DIALS NUMBER)
(LINE RINGS)
This is Detective Robertson.
Leave a message after the beep.
- (BEEP)
- Where are you?
Where the hell are you?
You promised me that you would help me.
You said you'd get me out of this.
Now I'm so fucked.
Call me, asshole,
at least to tell me
that you don't give a shit
that you sold yourself
like all the other disgusting cops.
(CHUCKLES)
And I'm on my own.
♪ ...comfort and joy ♪
♪ Comfort and joy ♪
♪ O tidings of comfort and joy ♪
(VOCALIZING)
Shit.
- (RING-TONE CHIMES)
- Hello.
Hello?
(RING-TONE CHIMING)
- ♪ ...Christmas Day. ♪
- ♪ (CHIMING CONTINUES) ♪
♪ To save us all from Satan's power ♪
♪ When we were gone astray ♪
♪ O tidings of comfort and joy ♪
♪ Comfort and joy ♪
- (SECOND RING-TONE CHIMES)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
(GRUNTS, YELPS)
(RING-TONE CHIMES)
(MULTIPLE RINGTONES CHIMING)
Stop.
No.
(ALL RINGTONES STOP)
(GASPING)
(RING-TONE CHIMING)
(WINCES)
(CELL PHONE CHIMING, BUZZING)
(BEEPS)
MAN: Everly.
What a surprise.
I assumed you'd go down
without a fight.
I was wrong.
I'm never wrong.
Did you get my present?
Open it.
I picked it out myself.
(GASPS)
Your detective friend
is just the beginning.
221 Shaffer Avenue.
What?
My men are already there
waiting for my call.
No, Taiko. No.
No, Taiko. No. Please, no.
- We had an agreement.
- I'm begging, please.
Do as your told,
or I kill your mother and daughter.
Do anything you want to me, but, please,
please, just leave them out of this.
I don't need your permission to do
anything I want with you.
I own you.
- Yes. Please...
- Or did you forget that?
- If you ever loved me...
- This isn't about love.
It's about honor.
You were taken to be a whore,
just like the others,
but when I saw you, I said,
"No, she's special. She's mine."
But you betrayed me, Everly.
You... You're right.
You're right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I... I was scared,
and I deserve to die because of it.
But...
but, please,
please let them live.
Let them live, please.
(TAIKO SIGHS)
All right. I will grant you your wish.
You will die in that room tonight, Everly,
and I'll let little Maisey live...
Thank you. Thank...
just long enough
to earn back what you've cost me.
I'm sure your daughter will be
very popular with the older clientele.
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
(SPEED-DIALS)
Come on, Mom.
Pick up. Pick up.
- EDITH: Hello.
- (HANGS UP, SPEED-DIALS)
(LINE RINGING)
- Hello. It's Edith...
- And Maisey.
- We are not home right now.
- (HANGS UP, SPEED-DAM)
- (GROANS)
- Hello. It's Edith...
And Maisey.
- We are not home right...
- (HANGS UP, SPEED-DIALS)
EDITH: Hello.
- Hello?
- Mom.
- Everly?
- (SIGHS)
There's men there.
There's men already there.
You need to take Maisey and run.
What the hell are you talking about?
What men?
- Mom...
- Where are you?
(DOORBELL RINGING)
- (MEN YELLING)
- Who's that?
- They're there.
- (CLATTERING)
Everly, what have you gotten us into?
Mom, you got to get out of the house
right now with Maisey,
or they're going to kill you both.
- Okay, okay. I'm going. I'm going.
- Come on.
- MAISEY: Grandma.
- (DOGS BARKING)
- Maisey.
- I need you to be quiet.
MAISEY: Where are we going?
Who's out there?
- (CLATTERING)
- (MEN YELLING)
EDITH: Shh. Out the door.
We are going for a ride.
Follow me.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
While we are in the car, scoot over.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
- (MAN YELLING)
- (MAISEY SCREAMS)
- (CRASHING)
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
- (SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
- Mom?
- EDITH: Maisey. Maisey...
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
It's going to be all right, baby.
Keep your head down,
and hand the phone to Grandma.
Put on your seat belt.
Good job, baby.
Everly, what the hell
is going on?
Mom, you need to keep driving.
Don't stop for anyone.
Meet me at McCoy Park downtown.
- I'm calling the police.
- No.
He owns the police.
This is madness.
What do you mean?
- Who owns the police?
- (ELEVATOR DINGS)
No time.
Four years ago, you disappear,
and I haven't heard from you
in four years, Everly,
four years.
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
- (BEEP)
- men showing up at my home
in the middle of the night
to kill me and Maisey.
What have you done?
And why would we want
to see you, anyway?
First you abandon your daughter,
and now you put our lives in danger?
- MAN: Bitch!
- I did not abandon her.
You have no clue
what happened to me.
You need to see me so I can give you
enough money for you to disappear tonight.
You have to start a new life
where no one can find you,
or else you're dead, and Maisey's doomed
to a life of misery.
Calm down so we can talk about this.
You are not making any sense.
- But, Everly...
- Meet me at the park,
and call me when you're there.
I love you.
- Please tell me what...
- (RING-TONE CHIMES)
WOMAN: Taiko, what the fuck?
It's been raining fucking bullets
in here for the last 10 minutes.
Broke-ass motherfucker.
Listen, I've got a dead John
bleeding all over my place
because of that raggedy-ass bottom bitch.
What the fuck is
going on over there?
Oh, you know I can
fuck her shit right up.
How much we talking?
Damn.
That's all you had to say.
(BEEP)
Hello, boys.
Time to get motherfucking paid.
You, stay.
(GASPS)
Zelda.
♪ (ZELDA WHISTLES: "JINGLE BELLS") ♪
(WHISTLING CONTINUES)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING SLOWLY)
(WHISTLING, FOOTSTEPS STOP)
You shot your wad, bitch.
What?
(YELLS)
Die, bitch.
(CHUCKLES)
(BOTH PANTING)
(MOANS)
Die, motherfucker.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCREAMS)
I'm going to fuck you up.
(LAUGHS)
Fucking sai?
ZELDA: You bitch. Come here.
You want to fuck with me?
You fucked up, bitch.
I'm going to fuck you...
(GASPS)
- (FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
- (GUN CYLINDER SPINS)
(GUN CLICKS)
(FOOTSTEPS STOP)
Hi.
Bye-bye.
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPS)
Oh, thank...
- (CELL PHONE BUZZES)
- Shit.
Taiko is going to be pissed.
- Wait. Who did I just kill?
- Everly.
- Nice try.
- Wait. Don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
I can double that price.
I have a lot of money.
Bullshit! You don't have any money
or even go out of this apartment.
He doesn't give you any money.
You think you're better than us? Huh?
You're just his fucking slave.
- (GUN CLICKING)
- Listen to me. I can prove it to you.
I have enough money
for both of us, okay?
Bullshit. He doesn't
give you any money, bitch.
You don't have...
Okay.
Shit.
- Fuck.
- That's what I said.
Who the fuck did all this?
Did you do all this?
Is he paying you for each one?
Dena?
Everly?
You're not dead.
Sorry, sweetie,
but I need that fucking money.
Get the fuck out of here.
She's mine.
Elyse, you greedy bitch,
you have that money.
I don't need your fucking help.
She doesn't even have a gun.
- I got here first!
- You fucked up.
- Fuck you. Fuck you.
- You fucked up. It's my turn.
- You fucking bitch.
- You fucked it up.
- What are you saying?
- Fuck you.
- Fuck...
Fuck you.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (BODIES THUMP)
(SIGHS)
(COUGHING)
Oh, please. Oh, God.
Oh, God,
I don't want to die.
Please, help me.
Everly.
Please, help me, Everly.
I don't want to die.
Not like this.
I'm scared.
I don't want to die.
Then shut up for once
so you can save your strength.
(GUN CLICKS)
I understand you want to kill me,
but do you want to kill her, too?
Come on, help me.
Help me.
Please.
I don't want to die.
Just put some pressure
on here.
I'm scared.
I don't want to go to hell.
Okay.
Anna, you have to kill her.
I don't want to die alone.
I mean, I already know she's going.
You're going to be okay. Shh.
- What...
- Okay.
Shh.
- Put some of this on.
- Okay.
Okay.
(LIQUOR POURING)
Dena.
ANNA: Dena.
I'm sorry.
I have to do this.
If I don't, Taiko's going to kill me.
Anna, look around you.
- I can kill you, too.
- No.
We don't have
to do this right now.
I know I'm going to die tonight,
but I have a mother
and a five-year-old daughter,
and I have to do something
to make sure they're going to be okay.
Why?
- You were a mother once.
- Stop. Stop. Don't talk.
Please help me save my child.
After that, I will come back here,
and I promise it'll be you
who finishes this off.
How do I know
you're going to come back?
Because as long as I'm alive,
he will be obsessed with hunting us.
But once I'm gone,
he'll forget about them in time,
and they will be free.
I will make sure I die tonight,
but I don't want to give any of them
the satisfaction.
(GUN THUMPS)
I want it to be you.
Okay.
I'm going to give
you two hours, Everly,
but don't fuck with me.
Because if you can do all of this,
then I can do it, too.
Good luck.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (SIGHS)
(YELLS)
That's a lot of dead whores.
You don't get to call them that.
Get up. Now.
Can't.
(WINCES)
How bad is it?
It's pretty bad.
It's just a flesh wound.
It doesn't look fatal.
Can't say the same.
At least you don't feel anything.
(COUGHS)
Can I ask you a favor?
Seriously? (CHUCKLES)
I'm thirsty.
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING)
- You're welcome.
- (SLURPING)
(WAILS)
(GAGPS, YELLS)
Are you smiling?
Changed my mind.
(SWALLOWS)
(DOG BARKING)
We're too high up.
Don't even think about it.
Best-case scenario,
the fall kills you.
Worst case, you break your legs,
and the dog eats you alive.
Come here, Banzai.
- I hate that dog.
- (BANZAI BARKING)
Me, too.
You know guns,
and you're not a bad shot,
but you're not going to make it.
Tell Taiko he can lick my balls.
(GUNSHOT)
- Told you.
- MAN: My turn, bitch!
I'm nobody's bitch!
(GLASS CRASHES)
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINE)
No, please don't.
- Finally.
- (WHINE FADES)
Ralph.
- Sorry,
- (GROANS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hello.
- EDITH: Everly, where are you?
I thought you were
leaving 20 minutes ago.
I was. Just had to wrap
some things up first.
Of course. Maisey's cold,
and I don't like it up here.
I'll call you
when I'm on my way.
Okay.
(POLICE SIRENS BLARING)
Oh, shit.
(GROANS)
Great.
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
- MAN: Police, ma'am.
Ma'am, the building's
not safe. Open up.
NEIGHBOR: What's going on
out there?
I'm all alone, and it's the middle
of the night.
- Get out of here.
- Please open up, ma'am.
We're evacuating
the building.
NEIGHBOR: Why don't you get rid
of all those whores around here?
It's like in the Bible, you know,
Sodom and Gomorrah.
You have to evacuate the building, ma'am.
This way, please. Follow me.
I'm not going anywhere
until my daughter gets here.
That poor woman.
Her daughter's been dead for two years.
- Okay...
- Good night!
MAN: You have a video feed
of the building?
Fancy.
You know how much
he likes to watch.
I suppose it would be too much
to ask you
to kill me instead of have to face him.
I didn't join in.
I could have.
Oh, how generous of you.
Oh, wait. Should I be offended?
I was just following orders.
(CHUCKLES)
And that absolves you
of any responsibility?
No, but some of these guys
actually enjoy this.
The rest of us do it out of fear,
because if you don't,
Taiko will kill you or worse.
Taiko has forced me
to do so many things so vile,
human trafficking,
sex slavery.
Gang rape.
Talk to God.
I'm not interested in your confession.
Wait.
Don't leave the video for him to see.
Don't.
Trust me. Destroy it.
- (EVERLY YELLING)
- (MAN GRUNTING)
(RECORDING CONTINUES)
(MEN LAUGH)
(YELLING, GRUNTING CONTINUE)
(MAN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
- (SPEAKING JAPANESE)
- No!
(RECORDING STOPS)
(SWALLOWS)
Look at me.
Our worst day could be
a blessing in disguise.
Sayonara, Dead Man.
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR RUMBLES)
(COUGHS)
Come on.
You can.
(COUGHS)
(YELLS)
Taiko says he'll be in touch.
You have yourself
a merry Christmas.
OFFICER: We've got
her pinned down.
That's a lot
of dead whores.
Asshole!
There's no point in squeezing
your ass after passing wind.
Callate, pendejo.
(COUGHS)
I told you.
There's no way out.
What are you going to do?
Either you can help me
or shut the fuck up.
- May I suggest an idea?
- No.
Something my grandfather
would say.
I think I had my fill of Buddhist proverbs
for the day, Dead Man.
A sanctuary sometimes resides
in the eye of the storm.
(FOOTSTEPS THUMPING OVERHEAD)
(SPEED-DIALS)
Mom. I'm sorry.
I cannot get out of here,
so you're going to
have to come to me.
You need to get rid of your car.
It's probably being tracked.
EDITH: What? No, no, no, no.
I am not giving up the car.
Forget about your car.
Forget about your house.
You must come get
the money and vanish.
- Isn't that dangerous?
- Well, of course it's dangerous here,
but it's dangerous everywhere.
- I don't know.
- Listen. Listen.
I have a plan.
Come over here.
When you're getting closer, call me,
and then I'll explain to you
exactly what to do.
- Where are you?
- 157 Hopper Avenue.
I am afraid.
I'm scared, too.
I'll call you when I'm there.
So...
we are having company.
You may want to clean up.
Shit.
(BIG BAND MUSIC PLAYS)
♪ Deck the halls with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly ♪
♪ Don we now our gay apparel ♪
♪ Fa la la, la la la, la la la ♪
♪ Troll the ancient yuletide carol ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
♪ See the blazing Yule before us ♪
♪ Strike the harp, and join the chorus ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
♪ Follow me in merry measure ♪
♪ Fa la la, la la la, la la la ♪
♪ While I tell of yuletide treasure ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SCREAMS)
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Deck the halls with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la ♪
♪ La ♪
(MUSIC ENDS)
Do you think Maisey
would like this dress?
(GRUNTS)
What?
I think maybe
you should wear something
a bit more practical,
just in case.
(SIGHS)
Yeah.
Better?
Yes. Much better.
(COUGHS)
Now, what am I going to do with you?
Could I ask you for a last favor?
Why not?
Can you light me a cigarette?
You know, smoking will kill you.
Arigato.
One thing
I don't understand,
how were you able to get
to the police?
They got to me.
One day, my toilet broke,
and a plumber showed up
that was not really a plumber.
He promised to get me out of here
and into the Witness Protection Program
if I helped him.
Weren't you afraid
that he would find out?
Every minute of it,
but I kept thinking,
if they get the motherfucker,
I can go back to my family.
(CELL PHONE RINGING, BUZZING)
Are you guys here?
EDITH: We are walking into the lobby now.
Tell them that you're coming
to see your mother,
- Mrs. Haberdash...
- Haberdash?
That she's been complaining
about somebody trying to get her out
of her apartment, 7E.
Get off on the seventh.
Take the stairs to the sixth.
I'm at the end of the hall.
I'll be waiting for you.
Seventh floor. Okay.
(SIGHS)
Are you ready
to meet the family?
- Are You?
- (SIGHS)
This way, Maisey.
Stay with me.
Mom, say something.
- DOORMAN: Can I help you, ma'am?
- Say something.
Yes, we are coming to visit my mother.
Sorry, ma'am.
We had an incident earlier.
Who exactly are you going to see?
Um, Mrs., um...
Haberdash. Haberdash.
- Haberdash. 7E.
- Yes.
She's just calling me about
these strange people
trying to kick her out
of her apartment.
This used to be
a very nice neighborhood.
Right, Mrs. Haberdash. Lovely lady.
Tell her sorry for the noise.
Like I said, we had an incident.
It should all be over soon.
Thank you. Come, Maisey.
Mmm-hmm. Come, come, come.
We are in the elevator.
Be right up.
- Six.
- Seventh!
- What, Mom?
- Siete.
Oh, no, seven.
My mistake. (LAUGHS)
MAN: Seven.
You're doing good, Mom.
Thank you.
(BEEP)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(BOTH YELLING)
(YELLING STOPS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(SIGHS)
Hi, Mom.
Hey.
I'm...
Everly.
You were such a little girl
last time I saw you.
Can we continue this inside, please?
No, Mom.
There is no time.
You have to take the money and go.
I'm sorry.
Seriously, you have to go.
- Cartoons.
- Hush. Not right now.
Aw, but, Grandma...
- Hello.
- Hajimemashite.
- Who is this?
- This is...
a long story.
(WHEEZING CHUCKLE)
Maisey.
You don't need to be afraid of me.
You know what?
I think I have something
you might like.
It's a Christmas gift.
It's for a very special little girl.
Would you like to see it?
I'm sorry. I didn't have time
to wrap it.
She's been waiting for you
for a very long time.
Would you like to hold her?
- (BEAR GIGGLING)
- You like Pinky Bear, right?
- Yeah.
- What do you say?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- (BEAR GIGGLING)
- She is very pretty, like you.
Well, I would love
for both of you to stay,
but I understand you need to go.
If they ask you
about Mrs. Haberdash,
just tell them that you need
to put this in the car
and that you're
coming back to get her.
Maisey, I need to speak
with Everly in private.
Stay put right here.
Don't move.
Don't touch anything
or anybody, okay?
Mom, we really cannot do this now.
I am not going
to ask you twice.
Where is the bathroom, please?
What?
Keep an eye on her.
OK.
Hi.
(COUGHS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Sit down.
And now you're going to listen to me.
Look at me!
Do you have any idea
what you've made me go through?
of the nights I've spent,
tortured by thoughts
that you became a street junkie?
Or that you were dead somewhere
and I was powerless to help you?
Then out of the blue, her highness
calls me in the middle of the night...
and tells me to come
to this royal apartment!
Was I such a bad mother?
No, Mamá.
Let's not talk about me,
forget about me...
But Maisey?!
She needs you.
What type of mother are you?
You never sent her
a single birthday card,
or a Christmas card...
Not even a phone call!
Are you listening to me?
(SOBS)
But... I'm just so happy
that you're alive.
Honey, I've missed you so much.
But now...
You need to help me
understand what happened.
Please. Tell me.
I don't know where to begin, Mama.
There's so many things
I'd like to say to you.
But I can't.
There's just no time.
I can tell you this.
I was taken against my will
to be someone's slave.
I've been locked up in this apartment
for four years.
I... I don't know
if you understand that.
I'm so sorry.
What are you doing here?
Just visiting.
(GASPS)
What's that?
Don't go over there.
Why not?
Because I need your help
with something.
What?
I wanted to sing a song for you,
but I forgot the words.
What song?
"Itsy Bitsy Spider."
I know it. I know it.
(COUGHING)
Are you sick?
I am,
but singing always
makes me feel better.
♪ Itsy bitsy spider ♪
♪ Crawled up the waterspout ♪
♪ Down came the rain ♪
♪ And ♪
♪ Flushed the spider out? ♪
You're funny.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
I did not want you to get
involved in this.
I did everything I could
to protect you.
Who is this man?
He's the Devil.
What did he do to you?
Did he torture you?
No. I am luckier than most girls
that get sent overseas or stuck
in a dungeon
where they are raped constantly.
They don't even last that long.
For me, my worst torture
was losing my child.
That's it.
It's over. I am here,
and we are leaving
together right now. Let's go.
Mama, this is
not a telenovela.
Who do you think you are?
Forget about me.
I don't want you to be
a part of this world.
- (RINGTONE CHIMING)
- What's that now?
- (MUFFLED YELP)
- (CHIMING CONTINUES)
EVERLY: That's who he is.
That's what he brings,
mierda, muerte.
You must leave without me
so you can protect Maisey.
Do you understand now?
Hey.
Where did you go?
(FOOTSTEPS)
Is this a Christmas present?
Not exactly.
(WEAKLY)
Everly.
- It's wet.
- Everly.
Can I open it?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
- Everly.
- What do you think it is?
I couldn't even imagine.
Come on.
You are not
leaving here alive,
are you?
Sorry, Mommy.
MAN: Everly.
No! No!
Stop. Stop.
Don't touch that.
I'm sorry, honey. No.
My sweet little...
Are you hurt?
- Oh, my.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I screamed at you, honey.
- You know, that gift was not...
- (GASPS)
For little...
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Sweetheart.
(DOG BARKING)
Maisey.
Maisey!
(BARKING)
EVERLY: Oh, honey, come...
Banzai.
Hey, Banzai.
Banzai...
kill!
(WHIMPERS)
(GROWLING)
Banzai, no! Not him, her!
Banzai, kill that bitch!
- Banzai...
- (CLICK)
- (WHIMPERING)
- ball!
Oh, shit.
Banzai, no!
That's not a ball!
(WOOD CREAKING)
Mom?
- Mom?
- EDITH: Everly.
It's okay.
You can come out.
Oh, that doggie
was scary, wasn't it?
I'm going to show you
a trick, Maisey.
When things get scary,
you close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
You imagine snowflakes,
and you start counting the little,
tiny snowflakes.
- One, two...
- Why we are watching television now?
Three...
Shit.
- Don't say that.
- Sorry.
- Shit.
- Let's go.
Seven,
- eight...
- We can make it.
Nine,
- Ten...
- Okay.
- Stay there. Stay there.
- 11...
- 12...
Anna, open the door, please.
Anna, my little girl is here.
Can she watch cartoons in your television?
Ten minutes.
- Ten minutes.
- 16...
I just got to take care of some business,
but it's coming up the elevator.
- (ELEVATOR CLINGS)
- And then I'll come back up, okay,
and I'll pay my debt, but just
let them in for 10 minutes.
Come on.
Both of them. Come on.
Just keep them there
for five minutes,
five minutes.
Come on, Anna.
Okay, for her.
- Get in.
- Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Deal's not done.
- I understand. I understand.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- (GASPING)
- (YELLING)
(CABLE WHIPPING)
(RUMBLE)
Holy shit.
(SLOW CLANKING)
(GUN SLIDE CLICKS)
(MACHINERY THUNKS, WHINES)
What the fuck now?
(GASPS)
Where are...
(GROANS)
(CLANKING, CREAKING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Good evening.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
You may call me...
(SPEAKING ENGLISH)
The Sadist.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
And this...
is my...
(SPEAKING ENGLISH)
Masochist.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
I am a piece of dog shit!
(YELLS)
I'm so sorry. Thank you!
(YELLING)
(YELLS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE) I am truly sorry
for you that our paths have crossed.
Though if it's any consolation,
I believe we will make magnificent art
together, if only for a moment.
(COUGHING)
Let's start our show!
(EVERLY GASPING)
Clean that up.
And bring the cage.
(EVERLY GAGS)
(SOBS)
(EVERLY GASPING)
Put her in the cage.
No.
No!
(SOBS)
(WAILING)
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
Spectacular.
Truly spectacular.
(CHUCKLES)
Taiko has immaculate taste.
I approve.
(CHUCKLES)
She is worthy.
I am...
a make-up artist.
These are my make-up tools.
You shall be the heroine
of our show tonight.
Sulfuric acid.
Gasoline.
(SOBBING)
EVERLY: Oh, God.
Battery acid.
Sodium hydroxide.
No, no. (SOBBING)
And this one...
No, no.
No. No.
What are you going to do to me?
(MUFFLED YELLING)
(MUFFLED)
No, no, no!
Stay away from me!
(SOBS)
No. No.
- H2O.
- (GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
- (THUMPING ON CEILING)
- Quit with the noise!
That's it. I'm coming down there.
- (SPEAKING JAPANESE)
- I'm going to give you a what-for...
(THUMP)
(GASPING)
You killed her.
Where should I start?
Let's begin with your pretty face.
But by the end...
I will make it a masterpiece.
Do it.
- (GASPING)
- (CRACKLING)
Enough.
This one's nasty stuff.
I usually use this in the third act...
But you have spirit.
Please stop.
No.
So I'll let you know
what happens at the climax.
No. No.
No.
A prelude...
No!
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(SOBBING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPS)
My sincerest apologies.
This is most unprofessional.
Take her to the chair.
Don't touch her.
Don't you fucking touch her!
Stop! No, don't!
But good timing!
For the rehearsal of the perfect show,
I can use her as your understudy.
Let's skip to the last scene.
I'll show you the climax.
No. No, no.
So, this is your mother.
I see the resemblance.
Hold her head.
Stop!
If she dies, you die slower.
Mothers protect
their children to the death.
No.
(GRUNTING)
Mom, don't swallow it!
(GASPING)
(YELLS, GURGLES)
No. No.
(MUFFLED YELLING)
- (GROANING)
- Come on, Mama. Mama.
Wake up. Look...
(GROANS)
Mom, come on.
You have to throw up.
Come on, Mom, please.
Throw up.
(GAGS)
Come on!
That's okay.
- (GASPING)
- It's okay.
- (COUGHING)
It's okay.
(EVERLY GRUNTING)
(GURGLES)
Cheers, motherfucker.
(GURGLING)
(STOMACH GURGLES)
A fitting end.
(STOMACH GURGLING)
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
(LAUGHS)
(GAGGING)
It's okay, Mama.
It'll be all right.
It's going to be all right.
(MACHINERY WHIRS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(COUGHS)
What more do you want,
you son of a bitch?
Haven't you had enough?
With a show like this, never.
By the way, how's your mother?
These past few hours,
it's been extraordinary,
but now it's time
to watch you truly suffer.
Your mother has fought
the good fight.
Now it's time for you
to say goodbye.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(TAIKO LAUGHING ON CELL PHONE)
(SOBS)
Everly.
Pick up the phone, Everly.
I'm not done with you yet.
I wouldn't do that.
Fuck you.
(DOG BARKING)
Everly!
(SIGHS)
(GUN CLICKS)
(GROANS)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GRUNTS)
(RADIO CHATTER)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (RADIO SQUEALS)
Man down!
Alpha Team down.
Bravo Team, go.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(YELLS)
(GUNSHOT)
All clear!
(GASPING)
(GAS HISSES)
Happy holidays, Everly.
(GROANS)
Take her to the bed.
Put the rope around her neck.
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
Leave.
(GASPS)
And so it ends,
not with a bang,
but a whimper.
You are nothing.
You don't exist.
This is all a nightmare.
If I die, it'll be like waking up.
And if I don't...
it'll be your nightmare, motherfucker.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
You have been a revelation.
But don't kid yourself.
You have only gotten so far
because I allowed you to.
If you're going to do it, just do it,
and shut up.
After all you've
been through tonight,
did you really think
I would make it that easy?
Yeah.
Why haven't you killed me?
Maybe you can't bear
the thought of living without me.
Maybe no matter what I do...
you just don't want me gone. Hmm?
Maybe I go across the hall
and get your daughter,
make her watch the rest of this.
Does little Maisey know
that her mother is nothing but a used,
discarded whore?
Keep my daughter's name
out of your mouth!
(KICK MISSES)
(CHUCKLES)
Your bastard child
should be honored
that I even know its name,
that I let it live,
in spite of its
traitorous mother!
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
(GASPS)
Frankly, death by my sword
is an honor you don't deserve.
(GASPING)
I would take your heart,
but your betrayal has shown me
that you don't have one.
You stole my life.
I owe you no loyalty.
I fucking hate you!
(GASPING)
I loved you.
Tough shit.
It's infinitely more painful
to remove a tattoo
than it is to receive one.
And the same is true for love.
(GAGS)
You don't have
to go through the pain
of removing your love for me...
so I will take back my tattoo
as a souvenir.
(CHUCKLES)
You branded me like a cow.
Take it.
- (GASPS)
- (YELLS)
Turn over.
I want to look at your eyes
when I kill you.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GASPS)
(CRACKLING STOPS)
(GROANS)
(SPITS)
If I die by your hand,
you and Maisey
will never be safe.
(GROANS)
Then die with honor.
Do it yourself.
What happened to honor in love?
(SIGHS)
You'll never know love like I do.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(LAUGHS)
(YELLS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(BODY THUMPS)
(TAPE RIPS)
(ZIPPER ZIPS)
MAISEY: What are you doing
with Pinky Bear?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Take Pinky Bear.
Take Pinky Bear,
and she'll protect you.
Okay? Yeah?
And promise she's going
to stay with you and you won't lose her?
Promise me.
Okay. Now, I'm going
to be right back.
Don't move.
(DIALS CELL PHONE)
- ANNA: Hello.
- 911. What's your emergency?
911? Yes, I need help.
There's a little girl...
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
- Ma'am, I'm going to need you
- to calm down.
- Who is it?
Can you tell me where you are?
- (POUNDING)
- Ma'am, please. Hello?
- Go away!
- Ma'am, are you there?
(DOOR CRASHES OPEN)
- If you're talking, I can't hear you.
- No, get out!
- (MAN GRUNTS)
- (BLADE SCRAPES)
Get out!
(ANNA SCREAMS)
- (BLADE WHOOSHES)
- (ANNA GASPS)
- (BODY THUMPS)
- All units, all units,
please be advised,
A.D.W. in progress,
157 Hopper Avenue.
Respond code three.
Ma'am, are you there?
MAISEY: Grandma?
OPERATOR: Ma'am, keep talking.
I'm not hearing you. Are you there?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Hello, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you there?
(WIND BLOWING)
Grandma!
(FLOOR CREAKS)
(BEAR GIGGLES)
If you're feeling scared,
you close your eyes
and count snowflakes.
- (FLOOR CREAKING)
- One, two...
- It's okay, little girl.
- Three, four,
- five, six...
- Open your eyes.
- Seven, eight...
- Turn around.
Nine, 10...
Turn around!
(GUNSHOT)
EVERLY: Maisey...
you're safe.
(GASPS)
Maisey.
Come here, honey.
I know I might look scary, but...
I would never do anything to hurt you.
Come sit with me.
It's over.
I know who you are.
You do?
You're my mommy.
I have your picture in my room.
That makes me very happy.
You know what?
I've always had
your picture with me, too.
And now I want you
to have it, okay?
I want you to keep it
and think about me,
my little girl.
Why were you gone
so long, Mommy? I miss you.
I miss you so, so much too.
And...
not one minute went by
where I didn't think about you.
(SNIFFLES)
I had a hole
in my heart right here
every second we were apart.
But today, when I saw you...
ah, Maisey,
you filled my broken heart.
I love you, always.
Always and forever?
Forever and ever.
I love you, Mommy.
(SIRENS BLARING)
Mommy?
(RADIO CHATTER)
Medics! Come!
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ All is calm ♪
♪ All is bright ♪
♪ Round yon virgin ♪
♪ Mother and child ♪
♪ Holy infant ♪
- ♪ So tender and mild. ♪
- ♪ (SIRENS BLARING) ♪
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ Shepherds quake ♪
♪ At the sight ♪
♪ Glories stream ♪
♪ From Heaven afar ♪
♪ Heavenly hosts ♪
♪ Sing, "Alleluia" ♪
♪ Christ, the Savior, is born ♪
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(FLATLINE TONE WHINING)
♪ Silent night ♪
♪ Holy night... ♪
I'll take it. I'll count the bag.
Come on. Hurry up. Here.
- ♪ All is bright. ♪
- ♪ Watch your hands. ♪
- ♪ Round yon. ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four, five, ♪
- ♪ Virgin. ♪
- ♪ Six, seven, eight, nine, 10, ♪
- ♪ Mother and child ♪
- ♪ 11,12,13,14,15... ♪
(HELICOPTER ROTORS WHIRRING)
♪ Holy infant ♪
♪ So tender and mild ♪
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
(FLATLINE TONE WHINING)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(EVERLY GASPS)
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS)
- (MUSIC FADES)
- (HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(BEEPING STOPS)
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly